Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
I heard Magnum
condoms are basically
the same size as
regular condoms.
Mmm-mmm.
Which makes you think. like.
what else do we believe
just because of marketing?
Like. if you grew up being told
the Book of Mormon is fake.
you'd probably believe
it was fake 'cause
that's what you were told.
No. Magnums are huge.
My sister said her ex-husband
had a scary big peen.
like. frighteningly big. and
they had to wear Magnums.
Sounds made up.
Elephant trunk.
Yup. That's what
she would call it.
I was watching this video.
I'm not sure where I saw it.
It was these two people
having intercourse.
um. sexual intercourse.
sex. and. uh. and a
cameraman filming them.
Like an amateur porno...
nography type thing?
Um. and the girl in the
video was moaning loudly.
as in typical. I assume.
in that kind of video.
Just screaming.
And then. all of a sudden.
off camera. in the hallway.
you hear this lady
yell. through the wall.
"We can hear you!"
And the couple stop sex-ing.
And the look of embarrassment
and horror on their faces
was so painful.
And the porno-girl who's. like.
taking it from behind-ish.
says something defiant. like.
"Good!" under her breath.
but you can literally
see her soul
being sucked out of her
body. right then and there.
All of her dignity gone.
as if realizing for
the first time. like.
"Wow. this is my life.
"I'm f-ing a stranger
on camera for money."
And I just thought.
"Like. wow. that is
really poignant."
Because. like. in that moment.
I was like. "Yeah."
God's real.
We have souls.
It's divine confirmation.
Do you watch a lot of...
No! I do not! No.
- I do not watch porno-ography.
- Okay. okay.
No.
- It's okay.
- No! I said no!
- I'm not!
- Mmm-hmm. I know.
- Not a pornography watcher.
- Okay. Okay.
Oh. I hope this goes well.
I know it's not a competition.
but I haven't baptized
a single investigator
on my mission yet.
It's okay. I've only converted.
- like. eight or nine people.
- Eight or nine?
Balls.
Anyway. what do you think
about what I was saying?
The porno thing?
Like...
How has God shown you
that the church is true?
I don't know. I guess
I haven't really...
I haven't really
thought about it.
But you know it's true.
If ye receive no witness
until after the trial
of your faith...
If ye receive no witness...
Who do we have...
after this couple again?
I think we have the bald
guy we met at Costco.
Okay. Oh. yeah.
Okay. for every
flight of stairs...
- Yeah?
- Our husband
gets five times hotter.
Hi. good afternoon. ma'am.
My name is Sister Barnes.
and this is my
companion. Sister Paxton.
Are you interested in learning
about our savior. Jesus Christ?
Okay.
- Hi!
- Good afternoon.
- Hi. are you interest...
- My name is. uh.
Sister Barnes. and...
You ever feel like
when you sing.
it's. like. too high or too low?
I don't really like to sing.
I think you have
a beautiful voice.
I know I don't have a
beautiful voice. but...
No. you do. You do.
I enjoy it.
Oh. my gosh. I already
love these girls.
Hey...
Sorry!
Sorry! Can we get a pic?
Oh. of course!
Uh. here.
- Is it true?
- Is what true?
- Do you wear magic underwear?
- What?
Oh. my gosh! Come
on. let's go.
This is it.
People think we're weird.
What do you mean?
I don't know. That
South Park musical
kind of makes fun of us.
I listened to some of the songs.
and they're actually
pretty funny.
Anyway. who... who
cares what people think?
You're awesome.
Thanks.
Hi. I'm Sister Paxton. Hi.
Hello. I'm Sister Paxton.
This is my companion.
Sister Barnes.
God chooses prophets.
such as Adam.
Noah. Abraham and Moses.
The prophets teach about
God and receive revelation.
All right.
Let's get you a baptism.
Okay.
Ah!
Good afternoon.
- Hi.
- Good afternoon.
I'm Sister Paxton. and this is
my companion. Sister Barnes.
Um. are you Mr. Reed?
I am. Hello to you.
- Hello. Wait.
- Hi.
You are Paxton. you are Barnes.
- Barnes?
- Um. no. I'm...
- Paxton. Barnes.
- Barnes. yes.
- Yeah.
Mr. Reed. it's so nice
to meet you. finally.
We were just in the area.
and we wanted to stop by
because you mentioned
you might be interested
in learning more about
the Church of Jesus Christ
of Latter-day Saints?
Yeah! Yeah. yeah. yeah.
Mr. Reed. we would like
to give you this booklet.
as it will help you
understand the restoration.
I... I actually
have one already.
but. um. you can
never have too many.
It... it tells
you all the ways
the Heavenly Father
can reveal His gospel.
- As a part of His plan...
- Thank you.
God chooses prophets.
such as Adam. Noah.
Abraham and Moses.
- Uh. prophets...
- Yeah. well. talking of Noah...
it is very. very wet.
Teach about God and
receive revelation.
and they interpret the
word of God. and preach
the gospel to the world.
and because of Apostasy...
Would you like to come inside?
People lose knowledge
of the gospel.
Do you have a girl roommate?
A girl. who?
A... a roommate?
We can't come inside unless
another woman is present
but. um. we can.
uh. stay out here
in the doorway. if
that's fine with you?
It's just for safety.
We don't mind the rain.
Well. my wife is
home. Does that count?
- Yeah!
- Perfect.
When you said "roommate."
I panicked. I...
I haven't had a
roommate since. uh...
Anyway. I... I have a soulmate
and that is good enough?
- Yes!
- That's great!
We'd love to come in
and meet your wife.
Then come on in! Great!
- Do you like pie?
- Yeah!
My wife has pie in the oven.
I've gained so much
weight on my mission.
People are always
feeding us treats.
We never seem to turn them down.
Well. my wife loves to bake.
- May I take your coats?
- Oh. yes.
I really love pie.
I'm super excited.
My grandma used to
make the best pie.
Okay. well. you and my wife
are gonna get on very well.
- Great.
- Oh. one thing.
the walls and ceilings
have metal in them.
- I hope that's okay.
- We don't mind.
Good!
Well. I will go and
check on the snacks.
Make yourselves at home.
Thank you.
My wife is being shy.
But the pie. the pie is nigh.
She'll have to be in
the room with us too.
Yes. of course! Of course.
right. I understand.
Please take a seat. take
a seat. take a seat.
Couple of colas.
Help... help yourself.
I think...
it is good to be religious.
Well. our work here is done.
No. I just want you to
know that before we start.
Yeah. I think that
we would consider
that refreshing to hear.
Well. sometimes. it feels like
maybe religion isn't at the
center of culture anymore.
Well. it's fading. isn't it?
Yeah. over time. Mm-hmm.
Okay. are you
ready to hear about
our Heavenly Father's
plan for you?
I am! Wait.
Where are you both from?
Me? Ogden. Utah.
One of eight
daughters. I know.
it's as bad as it sounds.
And Sister Barnes is
from Salt Lake City.
Uh. Philadelphia. originally.
Ah.
And you're both raised
in the church. yeah?
Born and raised.
My mother was a convert. so. um.
when my dad passed away.
we auditioned a few
different churches.
just to see what was out there
and see if we still
believed in it.
I know that feeling.
I know that feeling very well.
It's so important
to find your faith
in a doctrine you
actually believe.
and that's a very.
very personal struggle.
That is a personal challenge
that I have struggled with
for a very. very long time.
You know.
what is the one. true religion?
It's funny. Sister
Hall was telling us
that we should
prioritize other investigators.
- Oh.
- Oh. but no! I...
I'm just saying
that I could tell that you
are a very spiritually
curious person.
just like Joseph Smith.
You know. Joseph investigated
many different denominations.
Presbyterian.
Methodist. Catholicism.
And none of them quite fit.
which is why Joseph
founded our church.
Mm-hmm.
As I understand it.
stop me when I go wrong.
he was visited in the night
by an angel called Morony.
- Moroni.
- Moroni. Yeah.
Moroni. who showed him
where he could locate
some golden plates
near his home.
His mysterious translation
of those plates
form the basis of this.
Wow!
No. you read more than we do!
No. seriously.
we should be more
like you. Mr. Reed!
Mr. "Read."
The pie smells amazing.
And now that you've been
studying The Book of Mormon.
how does it make you feel?
Can you guess what kind
of pie she's making?
Is it...
blueberry pie?
It is blueberry pie!
Yes! I knew it!
My favorite!
Going back. can I ask
how did your father pass away?
- Um...
- I'm sorry.
- I shouldn't...
- Lou Gehrig's disease.
Blueberry disease?
Okay. that's...
That's... that's wonderful.
blueberry disease.
Who wouldn't want that? Yeah.
Uh...
Lou Gehrig's disease.
Gehrig's.
Oh. that's... that's awful.
I'm so sorry. I...
I... I misheard.
That is a malicious affliction.
I... I thought you
were making a joke
about the pie. I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Have you seen any signs of
your father since he passed?
Has he tried to communicate
from the other side?
Mmm. no.
Strange.
Well. I'm...
I'm really sorry. and
I'm sorry about the...
blueberry mix-up.
It's okay.
When I die. I want to
come back as a butterfly.
just to follow around
the people I love.
I'll land right on their hand.
Not their arm. not
their... their head.
right on their fingertip.
so they know it's me.
Ah.
That's sweet.
Oh!
Apologies! That is a
foible of the house.
I'm sorry. It does
that. It does that.
Um. well...
Ladies. I can't see you now.
- Um. I think it is time.
- Hmm.
Time for what?
Time for pie!
Pie!
Woohoo!
And. uh. time for enlightenment.
Oh?
I'm sorry. I should
have offered you water.
The word of wisdom forbids
caffeine and
alcohol. doesn't it?
Well. it doesn't. uh.
specifically mention soda.
Sure. it may be healthier
to avoid caffeinated drinks.
but we're just not thirsty.
Aha.
How do you feel about
awkward questions?
The meme?
Heh. no. I want to
ask an awkward. uh.
an icky question.
an insensitive
question that I think
will add depth to
our conversation
very quickly before
the sun goes down
and we're done for the evening.
But only if you're
comfortable with that.
Well. we won't know
if we're comfortable
- until you ask. so...
- Fair point.
Maybe you just ask?
Okay.
If you don't ask.
I'm gonna leave here wondering
what we missed out on.
Very well. My question
is this. Um...
Now I feel it's been
built up to. Uh...
Should I request a drum roll?
I'm going to
request a drum roll.
A drum roll please. ladies!
Keep going! Keep
going! Keep going!
More! More! More!
Now. I... I... I...
my question is.
how do you feel about polygamy?
How do you... how do you
feel about the concept of
a man having multiple wives?
I mean. it's... it's
not for me. um...
Are you asking from a
biblical perspective?
Uh. Mormonism has a
controversial history
with the misogynist practice
of men claiming multiple wives.
But I am fascinated by the
idea of Modern Revelation.
which was used to
erase this behavior
from the church in 1890.
I just think that's
worthy of conversation.
Yeah? Uh...
And what I mean by that
is that we're
discussing a church that
decided that a
controversial practice
was a stain on its reputation.
and an actual hindrance
to recruiting new members.
and so it used revelation.
word of God told
unto the prophet
to banish a provocative
religious pillar
that seemed unsavory
in contemporary times.
Yeah. I know that. um.
it may be difficult
to understand. um.
but. uh. polygamy was
a spiritual mission
needed at the time in order
to grow the ranks
of our membership
in the wake of much
hardship and bloodshed.
Um... a man having
plural wives
meant more... more babies
to help the community grow.
Hmm.
It's. yeah. it's
sketch for sure.
- to our modern brains.
- And it was...
it was removed from the
church not just because
it was grotesque
or controversial.
but just because it
wasn't necessary anymore.
You see. I worry. and...
forgive my loud language.
uh.
I worry that Joseph Smith
used the concept of polygamy
to legitimize his
affairs with other women.
I worry that Joseph's
wife. Emma Smith.
was upset when he
slept with Fanny Alger.
their sixteen-year-old maid.
I worry that he
formulated a plan
to use revelation for
consequence-free sex
in the aftermath of
that indiscretion
and others like it.
You know. "With great power
comes great responsibility."
Spiderman.
Voltaire.
Right.
I guess what I would pose
to the room is my concern
that polygamy has no
spiritual bearing whatsoever.
That is somewhat of a
distortion. I think...
The church's own
history corroborates
and implies this...
cynical brainwashing tactic.
Is that true?
I... I... I'm sorry.
I... I'm not sure where
you're getting this.
If revelation by God
is filtered through man
and man is flawed and
man sins and man lies.
then how do we know
any of it's true?
We know it's true because
of how it makes us feel.
Bingo! That's exactly right!
That's exactly right.
Couldn't agree more.
It's our personal relationship
with God which matters.
Let us talk with our bishop
about some of the points
you're raising. Um...
Question. What's your
favorite fast food?
I try not to eat it.
None of us do. but go
on. we've all got one.
Um...
Okay. Burger King is better
than Carl's Junior...
What's Carl's Junior?
Hardee's on the East Coast.
Burger King is
better than Hardee's
which is better than Rally's...
- Rally's?
- Checkers.
Burger King is better
than Hardee's. which is
better than Checkers.
which is better than Wendy's.
which is better than In-N-Out.
which is better than McDonalds.
which is better than
Jack in the Box.
which is better than nothing.
Jack in the Box serves
breakfast all day.
I love breakfast!
What about Taco Bell?
We don't talk about Taco Bell.
Why don't we talk
about Taco Bell?
We'd have to talk about
Taco Bell to talk about...
why we don't talk
about Taco Bell.
All right. so... so
Burger King is number one.
- I think it's trash.
- Oh.
Right. Not Jack in the Box.
I vote Wendy's.
I could support.
Good! Wendy's it is. Yeah.
Do you know? I've
never had a Wendy.
That came out wrong.
It's okay.
So when I started
studying theology.
the last thing I wanted
to do was find...
the Wendy's of religions.
I was just writing
a research paper
for a college class. and I
was content with dabbling.
So. some McNuggets here.
BK Whopper over there.
whatever fit the mood.
As I studied the genres.
McD. BK. In-N-Out.
i.e.. Mormonism.
Scientology. Islam. Buddhism.
as I got closer to God
through genre and
rigorous study.
as I worked on my
personal relationship
with Heavenly Father. and
I think strengthened it.
do you know what I found?
The more you know.
the less you know.
And by the time I was
50. I was malnourished
from the fast food of religion
I'd been packing into my brain
for the best part of a decade.
Every sect. cult.
creed. denomination
all claimed to be the
one. true doctrine.
and yet none seemed true when
held under the microscope.
So I wondered what
else was out there.
I promise you.
the last thing I wanted to do
was find the one true religion.
But unfortunately. I did.
Can we meet your wife?
Please?
Of course. yes!
She just has to be
present. and we want
- to meet her as well.
- Yeah.
Sorry. I'll... I'll go ask.
Sister Barnes. I
don't... I don't know.
Yeah. I don't want to spook him.
but we should wrap this.
Any messages?
Nothing.
Okay. Um...
let's just politely
wrap this and head back.
Just the highlights...
And she is finally ready.
Sorry about that.
Come on through. She's
eager to... meet you.
There we are.
- This way.
- Okay.
One moment. Mr. Reed. Uh.
we're just getting a call
from the Relief
Society president.
- We'll be right there.
- Oh. do you need a minute?
Hi.
- This is Sister Barnes. Um...
- I'll wait.
- I'll wait on the other side.
- Yeah. Just one moment.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Should we leave?
- Now?
- Yeah?
- Yes? Yes.
What is it?
Our bikes.
Yeah?
They're locked outside.
So what?
He has our coats.
The key to the bike lock
is in my coat pocket.
So we need our coats.
Yeah.
- We do.
- I don't know. do we?
Walk back without
coats and bikes?
What is that. two miles?
No. I think it's four.
It's a little over
the top. but I...
I'm fine. I'm fine
to walk. yeah?
- It's stuck.
- Unlock it.
There's no... lock.
What? Pull harder.
Here. Here.
All right.
Is he still there?
Didn't we hear him leave?
Are you sure?
Should we ask him for help?
No.
Can you fit through this?
You crazy?
Um. we should try
Sister Hall. okay?
Or Elder Kennedy. just so
they know where we are.
It's not going through.
It's the storm.
Keep trying. okay?
Okay.
We ask for help. hmm?
It'll be fine.
Mr. Reed?
And there they are! Welcome.
Mr. Reed. you have been too
generous with your time.
Sister Paxton and
I were just saying
what a pleasure it's been.
Um. but we just got off
the phone with Sister Hall.
and she needs us to
return to the church.
- Oh! Oh. well...
- Unfortunately. yeah.
I won't keep you if
you wish to leave.
We've been summoned back.
Yeah.
Damn it! Damn it.
'cause we were just
getting started. weren't we?
You know. you had me
thinking that maybe you were
onto something with your visit.
I've been impressed.
but I understand.
Uh. yeah. your coats are here.
hanging on the back of the pew.
Excuse me one moment.
Yeah.
Key.
So... so we just.
uh. need your help
with the door. Um...
It's... it's a little tricky.
I'm sorry?
I think your door is
a bit stuck out there.
The door won't open.
The front door.
Yeah. the front door
won't open again.
It opened when we came in.
Yeah.
Maybe if you unlock
it. it will open?
No. no. I... I... I understand
what you're asking me.
but. uh.
the deadbolts are on a timer.
I got carried away
with our conversation.
I didn't realize the
brace had been set.
I should have pulled the
pin when you came in.
but I forgot. So
if you are now
regrettably ready to leave.
you'll have to exit through
the back of my house.
Uh. where?
Just through here.
Well. can you just unlock
the front one. please?
We would like to go that way.
Just so we don't
get turned around
and confused when
we get outside.
Yeah. it won't open
again 'til morning.
Please. sir?
Oh. I'm sorry.
I promise you. it's
safe to leave this way.
Huh?
It's a little unusual
to have a door
that. um. locks on a timer?
Uh...
Yes. well. I see that.
Yeah.
And it's...
Well. it's a little unusual
that it can't be unlocked.
No. I... I... I know.
I am self-aware enough to
know how this might look.
Older man. two young
women in his house.
but I assure you. you
are welcome to leave
through... through the back.
You saw my house from
the outside. right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Right!
So. you know it's
a tiny footprint.
The back of the
house is just there.
Yeah.
Anyway. I will leave you space
to make your decision freely.
Yeah.
To clarify. I am trying...
have been trying very
hard to make it a point
not to pressure you.
so you shouldn't
even feel the need
to fabricate a story about
someone from your ward
calling you to leave.
It's... perfectly fine.
Leave when you want.
It wasn't an excuse.
they do need us back.
No. I know. but you're
saying you took a call
with someone from your ward.
Yeah. a moment ago.
But when you came inside.
I asked if you were okay
with the metal in the
walls and ceilings.
What do you mean?
I mean that the metal
obstructs cell phone signals.
so I do know you didn't
take a call. But...
Just to be clear.
so you're comfortable.
it is totally fine for you
to leave on your own accord.
You never need to feel
like you have to...
make excuses or...
or tell me little...
little... little white lies.
So which door takes us outside?
Pff.
Well... do you
have a preference?
Wh... why would I
Should we have a preference?
That is a fair question.
Not to be completely
weird. but can your wife
please just step in the room.
say hello and walk us to
the back of the house?
I'm not trying to be silly.
I promise. I'm really not.
but there are rules we follow.
and we were upfront with them.
I will ask.
Can I ask you a question first?
Do you...
still believe that my
wife is in the next room?
Despite all the evidence
to the contrary.
the scented candle.
the absence of an oven
with blueberry pie?
Or have you been
politely indulging a lie?
If you still believe that
she's in there. I'll go ask.
but it's something I
want you to think about
and maybe think about
in the context of your beliefs.
Do you believe in God because
somebody told you at
an impressionable age
that God is real.
despite having doubts
as you got older. despite...
seeing evidence to the
contrary your whole lives?
When your father lost
control of his body.
did you think it was God's
plan to ruin his life?
Or did you go on
believing something
that you know is not true
just to give you comfort
because you were afraid
of what it might mean
if it was all a lie?
I put the scented
candle on the table
because I wanted you to think
about the things
that you believe
just because somebody
asked you to believe them.
Can...
Can we use your phone?
Please?
I... I don't have a telephone.
You have a really
beautiful home. Mr. Reed.
It's like a church in here.
Did you build it yourself?
My wife built it.
We're gonna leave
through the back of your house.
Now. is that okay?
Of course.
Just like you said. it's okay.
and we can leave. right?
That's right.
What is it?
Sister Barnes?
That's a basement.
It doesn't look like
this goes outside.
I think that you can tell
that we're regrettably
uncomfortable with this
situation here tonight.
I'm sorry. but didn't
you just say a moment ago
that you saw the
outside of my house?
So then you clearly saw...
that the back of my
house overhangs a hill.
so you would know that
you have to go down...
in order to go out.
I think it would be best for you
and for all of us
if you could help us
go home because
the Stake President.
he knows where we are.
And the Ward Missionaries know.
And they'll be expecting us.
And there were witnesses.
weren't there. Sister Barnes?
On our way here. we
passed a police officer?
Whoa! The police?
I promise you.
you're getting way. way.
way. way too worked up.
Right.
But I think that we're scared
because you lied to us earlier.
Do you want me to help?
You asked me earlier
if you should
have a preference
between the doors.
I think you should. I
think it's something
you should consider
very carefully.
and then make the
right decision.
Do you want me to help you?
Yes.
Okay.
Then. please...
come and stand here.
Both of you come.
Just here.
That's it.
It's a simple choice.
But it should not
be made simply.
I need you to reflect
very. very deeply
and then make a
sincere decision.
Have you ever played
the Parker Brothers
game. Monopoly?
Monopoly is currently
published in 47 languages.
They sell it in
over 114 countries.
♪ If I could make a wish ♪
They say over a billion
people have played Monopoly.
But I'm guessing that only
a fraction of that billion
have actually finished it.
Maybe that reminds you
of something else?
Just a thought.
This is what most people mean
when they hear "Monopoly."
There's the pewter avatars.
Everyone has their favorite.
I shall not tell you mine.
Meow!
There's the pastel money
in various denominations.
and. of course. the jail.
Now. this next part
is very important.
Have you ever played the
1904 board game called
The Landlord's Game?
It is very nearly
identical to Monopoly
in every fundamental
way. There's the jail.
There's free parking.
There's fines and fees.
There's penalties.
For landing on other
people's properties.
and the ultimate goal
of forming monopolies
to force your opponent
out of the game.
What do games have to
do with us leaving?
Everything.
The Landlord's Game
was designed by
American feminist
Elizabeth Magie.
almost three decades before
a heater salesman
from Philadelphia.
Sister Barnes. changed
the name to Monopoly
and sold the concept as his own
to Parker Brothers in 1935.
This chap was called
Charles Darrow.
went on to become the first
millionaire games designer
in the history of the world.
while poor old Elizabeth Magie
died without ever being
credited for the impact
she had on American culture.
I'm talking to you
about iterations.
I need you to have a
very basic understanding
of iterating. because
I'm going to make
a very disturbing claim tonight.
It will make your
stomachs sink a little
and your hearts beat faster.
It will make you sick.
It may even...
I'm very sorry...
make you want to... to die.
Have you heard this song before?
You just played it.
No. I mean before tonight.
Mmm-mmm.
I disagree!
I think you've heard it
many. many times before.
but we will come back to that.
You are. are you
not. monotheistic?
We believe in
Heavenly Father. yes.
Okay.
There are three major
monotheistic religions.
Judaism. Christianity and Islam.
I call them. "The Big Three."
Judaism. i.e.
"The Original Edition."
Christianity. i.e. "The
Most Popular Edition."
and Islam. "The Newer.
"Second Most Popular Edition."
May I see your Book
of Mormon. please?
I'll give it back.
Thank you.
And finally. after
800 years. this!
Mormonism. i.e.
"The zany regional
spin-off edition."
These are all iterations
of the same source material.
These texts share many
of the same characters
and histories albeit presented
with different meanings
and perspectives.
So no.
I will not accept...
that you stand there
and tell me that
you've never heard
The Air That I Breathe
by The Hollies.
when I know that you have
heard Creep by Radiohead.
Oh. yes. you have. Come on.
♪ But I'm a creep! ♪
Yeah?
♪ I'm a weirdo ♪
Okay! "What the hell
am I doing here?"
I know these are things
you are thinking right now.
but they're also lyrics
you recognize. yes?
Yes?
The Hollies filed a plagiarism
lawsuit against Radiohead.
which they later
settled by proving
that the melody and rhythm
of The Air That I Breathe
appear in Creep.
How old are you? 19 or 20?
- Something like that. Okay.
- Hmm.
So maybe you know Lana Del Rey.
who remarkably was
sued by Radiohead
for plagiarizing
Creep in her 2017 song
Get Free.
Iterations.
Over time.
Diluting the message.
Obscuring the original.
Judaism is the OG
monotheistic religion.
It should. by a wide margin.
have the most number of
practicing members. And yet.
it makes up only 0.2% of
the world's population.
Why is that?
Why is the original less popular
than the iteration?
Is it any less true
than the others?
Are we talking about religion
or board games or music?
Yes.
It has the fewest members
because it doesn't advertise.
It doesn't have people like you.
knocking on doors.
selling people a better life.
a better board
game. a better song.
You ever think about that?
How missionaries are
really just salespeople
for an organization?
The product you're
selling is an idea.
You knock on my
door and you sell.
maybe I buy. maybe I don't buy.
Those are the
rules of engagement
when I invite you into my house.
We are negotiating a
transaction of ideologies.
And what I'm trying
to say to you tonight
is that I have an idea which
I would like to sell to you.
My argument is
that the holy texts
which we revere
are just mythological
iterations of stories
which ancient people have been
telling each other
for centuries.
They're not true or real
in any literal sense.
They are merely a conduit
to a more ancient truth.
The story of a savior...
who was born to a virgin.
who could perform miracles
and was supernaturally
resurrected.
was a very popular story
for at least a thousand years
before Jesus was born.
One of them has blonde hair.
one of them's brunette.
both dressed similar.
No. Never stopped by.
Mithras performed miracles.
He was marked by the
sign of the cross.
Horus. walked on water.
was crucified. had 12 disciples.
Krishna. he was a
carpenter. born to a virgin.
baptized in a river.
rose from the dead
and ascended into heaven.
This little gallery
depicts 12 gods
who were born on
December the 25th.
all of whom predate
the existence of Jesus.
I am sorry.
but it is impossible
to ignore the influence
of one narrative upon another.
or to ignore the fact
that all these stories
iterate into...
Star Wars: Episode I
- The Phantom Menace.
Can you imagine thousands
of years from now
people accepting Jar Jar
as a significant
religious figure?
Beg your pardon?
Jar Jar. Jar Jar Binks.
Jar Jar! Ex-squeeze me.
Never mind.
It is all terrifying.
isn't it? I'm sorry.
It is.
It is all...
Scary.
I'm scared.
I'm scared just saying
it out loud. really.
If God is real. and he
watches when we masturbate.
and he has such a fragile
ego that he only helps us
when we beg him and
shower him with praise.
and he hates gay people
for being what he
made them to be.
well. that's terrifying.
If there's no God
and we're just horny.
microscopic ants
floating on a rock through space
with no divine purpose
and no hope to
achieve eternal life.
well...
that's terrifying too.
"Either the church is
true or it is a fraud."
"It is the church
and kingdom of God.
"or it is nothing."
Do you agree with that?
Would it help if I told you
this is Gordon B. Hinckley.
the 15th President
of your church.
- Do you agree with Gordon?
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thought you might.
So either it is all true
or none of it's true. yes?
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Then I want you to
choose which door
to go through based
on your faith.
Are...
are you asking us
for us to deliberate our
belief in the church?
Is that a factor
which will correspond
to us going home?
I'm asking you to
choose between belief
and disbelief.
My own claim is that all
10.000 verifiable religions
that exist in the world today
are as artificial as
the symbolic church
you are currently standing in.
It is farce.
There is nothing holy here.
Your religious text
is mere ornament...
as hollow and as capitalistic
as these ridiculous games.
I want to know what is
going to happen to us
- before we choose.
- I don't even know
how to begin to
answer that question
if it hasn't happened yet.
Wow. Mr. Reed.
you've introduced a lot
of interesting points.
I think we can admit that
you're a very smart man
and we still have
a lot to learn.
So with that. I
would like to agree
that you've...
convinced us.
and we'd like to leave
through the disbelief
door and go home now.
Right. Sister Barnes?
Sister?
Sister Barnes?
I think we should
listen to our super neat
and thoughtful host and
choose the right door?
You know. choose the "right"?
Like they taught us in primary?
It doesn't...
matter what you say to him.
He's not gonna let us go
just because we
admit he's right.
Let's just get out of here
while our host is being
gracious enough to let us leave.
I think that we're
being studied.
I think he wants to
learn something about us
based on which door we open.
Is that the game?
Someone scratches their
neck. and he's watching.
We say the wrong thing. and
he stumbles on his words.
A candle flame flickers. and
it captures his attention.
What have you been looking for?
What have you found?
If I'm right.
then the only thing
that matters right now
is what we actually believe.
And because I think
your rhetoric is thin.
and your garage sale
board game metaphor
is kind of offensive.
I mean. you asked why
Judaism only makes up
0.2% of the world's population
but didn't even pause
for the Holocaust.
You make no acknowledgement
of the religious persecution
Jewish people have faced.
You just use it as a setup
to a punchline
about missionaries.
And then. you skip over the fact
that none of this
addresses Islam.
as Muslims don't even believe
Christ was resurrected.
And then. you point out
all the similarities
these mythological
gods have with Jesus.
but breeze over the many
glaring differences!
One of these guys has
a freaking bird head!
I don't think... that
my point of view...
fits into belief or disbelief.
I think there's
an entire spectrum
that your game is neglecting.
So it doesn't matter
what I believe. does it?
Sister Paxton. do you
still believe in God?
Yes.
Then let's leave through here.
Let's be honest and sincere
and let God decide what
happens next for us.
Okay. we're leaving now.
Thank you for all
your mentorship.
and thank you for
letting us leave.
Are you coming too?
Sister...
It's okay.
One step at a time.
We'll go slow.
Sister Barnes. there's nothing.
It's all blocked off.
What do you think he wants?
Is he gonna keep
us here forever?
No. he's too smart. He...
He knows an Elder will
check on us. and...
which means he'll either
have to let us go or...
kill us.
From now on. if he lands
a philosophical point
that we don't agree
with. we challenge him.
We make him think.
He doesn't have
to steam roll us.
We might not be a
physical threat.
but we can be an
intellectual one.
I think that window
has a cage on it.
You're right.
He's coming. He's coming.
Take this.
Take this. Put it back.
If anything happens.
you take this.
and you stab him
in the neck as hard
and as fast as you can.
- No! No. no!
- It has to be you.
He's watching me too closely.
- He won't expect us to do it.
- Sister. no!
Okay. Let's have a code word.
Okay? Um...
Hey. if I say "magic underwear."
that means stab. Okay?
He's coming.
Magic underwear. That's
the code word. Okay?
Mr. Reed?
Mrs. Reed?
Is that you?
What's happening to her?
♪ But I'm a creep
♪ I'm a weirdo
Mr. Reed?
Where are you?
♪ Couldn't look
you in the eye ♪
♪ You're just like an angel
♪ Your skin makes me cry
No.
♪ And I'm a creep
♪ I wanna have control
♪ I want a perfect body
♪ I want a perfect soul
♪ I want you to notice
♪ When I'm not around
♪ You're so very special ♪
♪ But I'm a creep ♪
♪ I'm a weirdo
♪ What the hell
am I doin' here? ♪
♪ I don't belong here ♪
I had to be sure
before I introduced you to her.
Sure about what?
You are now in the presence
of a living prophet of God.
The reason I invited you
into my sanctuary
tonight is because
I have been shown a miracle.
I believe this miracle is proof
that all known religions
are demonstrably false.
and only an ancient
echo of something true.
I need a witness.
you. to verify that
the miracle is real.
Now. our family recipe
for blueberry pie is.
I think. a traditional one.
The ingredients include
butter. flour. corn starch.
sugar. lemon.
blueberries. of course.
but tonight I've also
included some wolf's bane
and some belladonna.
which means that.
in a short while.
the Prophet will be dead
from consuming the pie.
Then.
you will witness a miracle.
By the grace of God.
she will be resurrected.
Now. feel her pulse. please.
Both of you.
I need you
to feel her pulse right now!
Acknowledge. please.
that her heart has
now stopped pumping.
Do you know how to do that?
Index and middle finger
on the side of the neck.
in the soft. hollow area
just beside the windpipe.
Both of you. please.
lift her head to be sure.
She moved! She moved!
That was just a catalytic spasm.
She's alive!
No! No. no. Not yet.
Chemicals being
released into her body.
Acknowledge. please.
that there's no pulse.
Acknowledge!
- No. No pulse.
- No pulse.
Thank you.
Acknowledge that she
is no longer breathing.
Do you feel a breath?
No. No.
- So she's dead.
- Yes.
Okay.
Thank you.
A moment longer. and you
will witness a resurrection.
She'll return and
she will tell us
what she saw in the afterlife.
Has the Prophet moved?
No.
Hello?
- No. No.
- Mmm-mmm.
All right. Just un momentino.
Only a moment longer.
The Elders?
- We scream.
But not until he
answers the door.
- He's coming back.
- Scream! Scream!
Coming!
Ah! Sorry!
I was at the back.
- No. I'm sorry to bother you.
- No.
I'm just in the
neighborhood looking for
two young ladies from my church.
Oh.
Is everything all right?
They can't hear us.
I'm sure everything's fine.
I was just wondering if they...
stopped by.
No. I'm sorry to say.
you are the first house
caller I've had all day. so.
- Did you see this?
- It's locked.
Help.
We can pull the rug.
The matches.
We start a fire.
smoke out the speaking
pipe to make sure
the Elder knows we're here.
Okay. But you did ask
for more information
on the church. correct?
Uh. this... this is
the which church?
The Church of Jesus Christ
of Latter-day Saints.
Yes. yes. yes. yes.
Pull. Careful.
Is there some other
way I can help?
Do you want to use my
phone. call the police?
- I could get my coat...
- No. no. That's fine.
And come help you look around.
No. no. no. no. no. I'm
sure they're not far.
Uh. thank you for your time.
All right. well. good
luck. Yeah. I mean that.
- Okay.
- Uh-huh.
No.
He's coming!
Yeah? Yeah? Any luck?
She moved.
- What do you mean?
- When we were gone.
No. you're remembering it wrong.
She hasn't moved at all.
Her head is different.
- That's where she was!
- It's not!
Sister. that's not how
I remember it. Please!
Please. just come on! Help!
Hold the sleeve up.
I'd be remiss if I didn't
ask you one question.
Have you received this booklet?
I have not.
but I will give it a look-see.
Try another.
I know.
Focus.
Faster.
Conductor...
says... my... name.
White... clouds.
Not... Heaven.
They... unplug...
my brain.
It is...
not...
real.
And. thank you. Prophet.
We are very grateful
for your passage
to the other side.
Your prophecy will be recorded
into our liturgical texts.
Come. You must be
exhausted. Take my arm.
Well. now.
You see. this is rather
interesting because...
I know that one of
you has been lying
since you first got here.
And do you know how I know that?
Excuse me. can I...
can I take that?
I know from the way
that the fire reacts
to each of you.
A.
B.
Yeah. One of you
has a very. very...
very big secret. but
we will know more soon.
There will be before
you saw a woman die
and come back to life.
and there will be after.
Books will be written about it.
So choose your words very
carefully when I ask.
what did you witness?
Tell me. Tell me what you saw.
How did she...
I don't know...
And if you didn't see
something transcendental.
you absolutely must tell me.
I don't know.
'Cause if I'm wrong.
I need to hear it.
That's why you're here.
It's a contrived experiment.
We are your prisoners!
- It doesn't make sense...
- Oh. pooh!
- We're all prisoners together.
- For us to have an opinion!
You must know by now
that any of us can leave
whenever we want. but
why would we want.
after what we've seen?
I saw it. I saw it.
I heard her describe
what she experienced
on the other side.
Great! What did you hear?
She said there was a conductor.
- Yes. Yeah.
- Did she mean angel?
She had a feeling
of disassociation.
a feeling that
something wasn't real.
That's it.
So now you know.
Now. we know?
Yeah. now. you know.
Know?
I can show you God.
If you're willing to die.
It... it can be painless.
It can be temporary.
Like the Prophet. you
can be brought back.
It doesn't have to be
frightening at all.
I'll tell you... I'll tell
you what's frightening.
Not knowing is frightening!
Where do we come from?
What are we doing here?
What's our purpose?
The terror of those questions
is why religions exist.
I can answer those
questions for you.
I can give you a comfort
no religion in the world
is capable of giving you.
It all makes sense now.
I've been asking
myself all night.
how is he gonna make
killing us our idea?
Sister Barnes.
you're in a muddle.
I know. I can't tell
if you're playing
chess or checkers.
Monopoly!
Come on. it was right there.
You didn't show us a miracle.
Okay. what did I show you?
That wasn't a miracle.
So you say. What
did I show you?
That was not a miracle!
What did I show you?
It was a magic trick.
A magic trick?
You wanna know why we
don't talk about Taco Bell?
It killed me when I
was four years old.
Fifty people were hospitalized
from an E. coli outbreak.
The kids at school
called me Taco Hell
'cause I was clinically dead
while doctors operated
on my kidneys.
When I was dead.
I saw exactly what
your prophet described.
A blinding white light.
clouds. but not Heaven. a
sense of wanting to return.
a feeling that my state
of reality wasn't real.
That wasn't a prophecy.
That was a near-death
experience.
When the oxygen
leaves your brain
or your heart stops
pumping. your mind
creates unbelievable things.
I think you've been
keeping this woman
on the edge of death in
order to ask her questions
about meaningless hallucinations
so that you can
substantiate your idea
of what the one. true
religion really is.
Did you know...
that when you
remember something.
you're really only remembering
the last time you
remembered that experience?
You're not actually
recalling the event.
So your memory of
dying at Taco Bell...
isn't really of dying.
it's of the memory of the memory
of the memory of the
memory of the memory...
stop me... of that event.
So you're remembering
a false correlation
with the experience
you've just witnessed.
But this. this is
happening right now!
That's why I think. Sister
Barnes. Sister Paxton.
that you really need
to pay attention
because I promise you...
we're not talking
about a magic trick.
No.
we're talking about
magic underwear...
Help me! Help!
She'll come back to us!
I promise!
Sister Paxton. do not be scared!
She will rise again.
Challenge him.
Debate.
Come on. now. Sister B.
Wakey-wakey!
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
whoa. whoa. whoa!
No. that's not it.
That's not it. That's
a... a mucky pup.
Let's have that.
Moments. It'll be moments.
Let's have one of
your drum rolls. yeah?
Whoop!
Hey!
I'm very sorry.
Something is wrong.
I'm now worried...
that she's not...
coming back to us.
Yeah.
Oh. yeah.
Yep.
Yeah.
There it is.
No. it isn't.
That was a vein.
A-ha! A-ha.
The implant.
This is why she can't
come back to us.
Take a look!
I'm very sorry.
But Sister Barnes.
she's a program.
She's not real.
Do you know what gave it away?
The candles.
What are you saying?
I don't understand.
No. no. I know.
I know. I know.
How could you?
Can you explain it to me?
Are you. Sister Paxton.
familiar with the Daoist concept
of "The Butterfly Dream"?
A butterfly...
A butterfly flaps its
wings and causes a typhoon?
That is "The
Butterfly Effect."
Common mistake. No.
"The Butterfly Dream"...
concerns an ancient
Chinese philosopher
who asked himself the
following question.
"Was I a man dreaming
"I'm a butterfly.
or am I now..."
"a butterfly dreaming
that I am a man?"
Come and sit down.
Come on. Here.
This is us.
You and me alone together.
That was Barnes.
Bye-bye. Barnes.
I have come to a
dark realization
that we exist inside a
simulation so advanced
that we cannot tell the
difference between real life
and artificial dream.
You heard the Prophet. She
said. "It is not real."
You see. fire dynamics are
very difficult to render.
I've noticed this
anomaly in its behavior
when it interacts
with simulated NPCs.
like poor old Sister B.
She couldn't come back
to us. but when you die.
finger. please. you
will pass through death
and wake up...
into the real world.
What do you think?
Yes. no. maybe?
Um...
That's a theory.
Well yeah. you're
very welcome to...
to challenge my
premise. I love that.
Go for it.
I don't think this
is a microchip.
Oh?
I think it's a contraceptive.
A... a birth control implant.
Huh.
Tell me. have you ever met
a Mormon missionary who
was on birth control?
Did "Sister Barnes" say
she was on birth control?
Our church would've made her
feel ashamed about it.
and she would've
been too embarrassed.
- Simulation theory is...
- Ah!
"Hypothesis." please.
Sorry. it doesn't matter.
Simulation hypothesis
is not testable. is it?
No. it's a matter of
belief. like any religion.
You either believe
it. green door.
or you don't believe
it. purple door.
With all due respect.
I...
I don't believe it.
I'm not smart enough to
say why. I just don't.
Do you believe the
miracle that I showed you?
Yes.
- Yeah?
- At first.
But now?
I think something
happened tonight
that you didn't expect.
It feels like
you're improvising.
trying to convince me
of a simulation theory
that's not sticking.
Am I right?
Uh. are you asking
me if you're right
that I am improvising
or you're right that
the simulation narrative
is not sticking?
Yes.
High-five.
So. in fact. you agree
with your friend.
You think that the Prophet
was just hallucinating
a meaningless.
near-death experience.
No.
I think you switched the bodies.
I just haven't
figured out how yet.
I switched...
the bodies?
The doorbell rang when
the Elder got here.
Which drew our
attention to the stairs.
You would have been
prepared for that.
When we came back downstairs.
I noticed the woman wasn't in
the same position as before.
It was similar...
Her head is different.
But it was not the exact same.
I think another woman who
looked exactly like her
came into the basement
through a hidden
door or something.
disposed of her body and then
took her place at the table.
I see.
And then. once we
got back downstairs.
she read off a scripted prophecy
that you prepared for her.
Except the last
thing she said was.
"It is not real."
not... real...
Maybe she was trying to tell us
that the miracle wasn't real.
Ah.
You see what I mean when I say
something happened
that you didn't expect?
I think you gave her a script.
and she went off the book.
and now you're
trying to recover.
Well. if that's right. then. uh.
there'd have to be another
way into this basement. yeah?
Shall we have a look?
I don't think there is.
No.
I'm not doing very well.
Sister Paxton.
Unless...
Which means that...
there would have to be
a dead body down there
if you were right. huh?
Correct.
How will you test your theory?
I don't know.
But will you go
into that hole and
see if there's
somebody down there?
If I have to.
Why would you do that?
Because I want to
know the truth.
and because the only
way out is through.
Robert Frost?
Swamp Thing.
Don't go into that cellar...
unless you are prepared
to discover the
one. true religion.
I knew it.
Hey.
Sorry about the cold.
Have you figured it out yet?
I think so.
So what is it?
What is the one. true
religion. Sister P?
It's...
When we first arrived.
you left us alone
in your living room.
We thought you were
talking to your wife.
but you were doing
something else.
I was.
You took a key from
Sister Barnes' coat.
went outside to unlock
our bikes and hide them.
I noticed your hair was
wet when you came back
with the drinks. like you
were out in the storm.
You did this. I assume.
because you didn't want
the Elder to find our bikes
when he came back
looking for us.
But there was something
else on your mind.
There was.
You returned the bike key
to the wrong coat pocket.
We thought this was
a mistake you made.
Key.
But now I know it wasn't.
Why?
You gave the bike lock
to one of your prophets.
instructed them to lock the
final cellar door with it.
But why. why. why?
Why did I do that?
Because you wanted me to know
the only reason I'm
standing here right now
is because it is exactly
where you want me
to be standing.
I'm not here because
I chose to be.
I'm here because you
made me choose to be.
Oh.
Because you want me to believe
the one. true religion is...
control.
That is exactly right.
Religion is just a
system of control...
It's okay.
I'll help you.
No. you see. that's
what's so interesting.
They don't want your help.
They... they are exactly
where they chose to be.
But you killed that woman.
I disagree.
She... She chose to
eat a poisoned pie
because of her profound faith.
It is called drinking
the... anyone?
Kool-Aid.
It is true...
that I keep these
ladies a little chilly.
and a little peckish.
for which I am very
sorry. Sorry. ladies.
But only for the same reason
that your church goes to Haiti
to give out Bibles
after a hurricane.
It's easier to control
someone who has lost...
everything.
You're absolutely right.
She did go off-book.
Why do you do this?
The question is.
why do you all let me?
Sorry...
You are here because
the ideas of others
have influenced every
single decision you've made
since the day you were born.
and I've been able to predict
every decision you would
make tonight because of that.
You have allowed them
to dictate every
decision of your life.
They decide who you worship.
where you worship.
what you worship.
They even dictate the garments
you wear under your clothes.
The what?
Your magic underwear.
No... No...
No...
Pray...
Pray.
Pray for us.
Praying...
doesn't work.
Have you ever heard of the
great prayer experiment?
They divided
patients into groups.
Those who received prayers
and those who didn't.
The results of the
study were conclusive.
It doesn't work.
But I think it's beautiful
that we all pray
for each other...
even though we all probably know
it doesn't make a difference.
It's just nice to think about
someone other than yourself.
Even if it's you.
I'm grateful for all the trials
you've given me in my life.
And for your path that
you've laid out for me.
Quietly.
Goodbye. Sister.
♪ Mama take this
badge off me ♪
♪ I can't use it anymore ♪
♪ It's getting dark
too dark to see ♪
♪ I feel like I'm knockin'
on Heaven's door ♪
♪ Knock-knock-knockin'
♪ Mama put my guns
in the ground ♪
♪ I can't shoot them anymore ♪
♪ That long black
cloud is comin' down ♪
♪ Feels like I'm knockin'
on Heaven's door ♪
♪ Knock-knock-knockin'
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm